# Svetomir Timotijevic

- WordPress Expert Junior -

I am a passionate WordPress Expert Junior who is willing to learn and improve personally. I wanted to get retrained because I realised that I would express my creativity and love of web design specifically through WordPress. As I began to research and learn more about Wordpress I realized - that's what I want to do.

# **Personal Info**



sveta.shady@gmail.com



Spanskih Boraca 4, Nis



060-60-50-651



<u>LinkedIn</u> GitHub

# Core skills

WordPress

HTML and CSS

SEO

Troubleshooting

Optimization

# Soft skills

Creativity

Problem Solving

Precision

Determination

Detail-Oriented

Communication

### **Environment**

Windows

# **COURSES**

July 2022 - September 2022

- 128 hours of theory and practice -

# **IT Bootcamp**

Web development (WordPress)

#### **GAINED SKILLS:**

- Creating well-designed, responsive WordPress websites by utilizing
  Page Builders and corresponding plugins
- Setting up **WordPress e-commerce platform**, including Shop, custom templates and payment gateway configuration
- Monitoring and improving website performance by using optimization best practices
- **Troubleshooting** WordPress issues (error 500, 404, mixed content, layout issues, plugin or theme conflict)
- Basic knowledge in HTML and CSS
- Familiar with PHP and phpMyAdmin

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

October 2010 - May 2016 Faculty of Law for Commerce and Judiciary,

Novi Sad

**Bachelor of Lows** 

September 2001 - June 2005 High school "Gimnazija", Kursumlija

**Department of Mathematics** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Technical inspection of the vehicle "Tehnik-Prom" Kursumlija

# **Bachelor of Laws**

January 2021 - present

- Vehicle Registration
- Creation of contracts and authorizations
- Creation of insurance policies
- Billing and payment
- Administrative tasks

Basic Court in Kursumlija

## **Bachelor of Laws**

September 2016 - September 2019

- Drafting court decisions in civil, criminal and executive matters
- Drafting employment contracts

## **LANGUAGES:**

- English: Advanced (C1)
- Serbian: Native

## **HOBBIES:**

- Fishing
- Sports
- Gaming